Partnership for Rural Improvement Records 1968-1985
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Lassey's Files, 6
  - PRI major features (Box 15, Folder 377)
  - NWREL-Agreement and budget (Box 15, Folder 378)
  - Earlier efforts in CE (continuing education) center and coordination of extension activities, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 379)
  - Correspondence, misc., 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 380)
  - PRI-draft proposal guidelines, 8-24-76 (Box 15, Folder 381)
  - Participants (address and phone numbers), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 382)
  - Faculty development program, 1975, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 383)
  - Kellogg foundation objectives for WSU proposal review, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 384)
  - Incoming correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 385)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 386)
  - PRI-EWSC activities, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 387)
  - PRI-WSU advisory committee, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 388)
  - PRI-position description, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 389)
  - PRI budget, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 390)
  - PRI projects summaries-eastern subregion, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 391)
  - CE task force report-references and appendices, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 392)
  - PRI projects summaries-eastern and western subregions, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 393)
  - PRI small group facilitation workshops, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 394)
  - PRI memos and misc., 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 395)
  - PRI projects update, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 396)
  - Alternatives for outreach-a summary, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 397)
  - PRI-barriers and facilitators, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 398)
  - Components and ideas for WSU outreach in continuing education, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 399)
  - CE task force-working paper #1, alternatives, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 400)
  - CE task force-working paper #2, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 401)
  - CE task force-working paper #3, CE center summaries, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 402)
  - CE task force-minutes with commendations, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 403)
  - Review of regional coordination committeed, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 404)
  - Task force for CE center at WSU, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 405)
  - Washington State Association of Counties: proposal for PRI, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 406)
  - Kellogg grant renewal, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 407)
  - CE task force-meetings with colleges, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 408)
  - CE task force report, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 409)
  - CE task force report, draft, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 410)
  - Hagood's letter re. Ed Moe and later correspondence, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 411)
  - PRI fellowship and task force brochures, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 412)
  - PRI planning, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 413)
  - PRI institutional development, 1977-1981 (Box 15, Folder 414)
  - PRI task forces, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 415)
  - Title V, RDACT, Legislation, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 416)
  - Incoming correspondence, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 417)
  - Leadership, rural planning and development, Kellogg, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 418)
  - Rough draft (Lassey, 8-13-73)-Rural Leadership Development (Box 15, Folder 419)
  - Moe, Ed- visit of, October 1974 (Box 15, Folder 420)
  - Rural development model draft, 11-1-74 (Box 15, Folder 421)
  - Incoming correspondence, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 422)
  - Proposal to Kellogg, November 1974 draft (Box 15, Folder 423)
  - Proposal to Kellogg, 12-20-74 (Box 15, Folder 424)
  - Institutional collaboration w. communities in rural development, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 425)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 426)
  - Notes on Kellogg (Lassey), 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 427)
  - Proposal to Kellogg, 2-17-75 draft (Box 15, Folder 428)
  - Conversation with Gary King of the Kellogg Foundation 7-2-75 (Box 15, Folder 429)
  - President's letter to Gary King, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 430)
  - Kellogg meetings-notes and comments on, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 431)
  - General notes and papers-Lassey, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 432)
  - Incoming correspondence, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 433)
  - Ed Moe, papers and contribution to PRI, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 434)
  - Proposal to the Kellogg Foundation, Sept. 1975 (Box 15, Folder 435)
  - Northwest regional educational lab; support agency guide-Jongeward, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 436)
  - PRI organizational alternatives, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 437)
  - Agendas of Kellogg meetings; things to be done by WSU Coordination Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 438)
  - Major features of the Kellogg proposal, by Lassey, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 439)
  - Kellogg administrative structure, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 440)
  - Kellogg organizational structure (charts, budgets etc.), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 441)
  - Kellogg agenda, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 442)
  - Kellogg budget and WSU responsibilities, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 443)
  - Re. Kellogg proposal, 1-21-76 to 6-23-76 (Box 15, Folder 444-445)
  - PRI: policy and advisory minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 446)
  - PRI policy council members, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 447)
  - Correspondence re. Kellogg proposal, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 448)
  - Correspondence with Gary King, Kellogg Program Director, 1976-1980 (Box 15, Folder 449)
  - Major features of PRI discussion paper, 4/16/76 (Box 16, Folder 450)
  - PRI working papers from 6-23-76 (Box 16, Folder 451)
  - PRI working papers from 9-1-76 (Box 16, Folder 452)
  - PRI working papers from 11-30-76 (Box 16, Folder 453)
  - PRI working papers, March, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 454)
  - PRI working papers, evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 455)
  - Inter-organizational development working papers, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 456)
  - PRI transparencies (Box 16, Folder 457)
  - Papers on organizational development; PRI regional coordination; PRI Title V, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 458)
  - PRI bibliography (preliminary), 1978 (Box 16, Folder 459)
  - PRI paper, Luther and Braglio, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 460)
  - PRI publication policy, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 461)
  - PRI case studies, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 462)
  - PRI papers-"Collaboration and integration in rural development by Lassey and Hagood (original copy) and a critique by Dan E. Moore of Penn. State Dept. of Ag. Economics and Rural Sociology (Box 16, Folder 463)
  - Papers by Lassey, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 464)
  - Paper for world congress of rural sociology by Lassey, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 465)
  - PRI monograph outline, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 466)
  - Task force working paper-Schwalbe, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 467)
  - Agenda, collaboration meeting, 4-16-76 (Box 16, Folder 468)
  - PRI meeting minutes, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 469)
  - Notes on Campfield sessions, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 470)
  - PRI work session, Jan.11-13, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 471)
  - PRI staff meetings, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 472)
  - PRI staff meetings, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 473)
  - PRI retreat, March 23-25, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 474)
  - PRI staff meetings, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 475)
  - PRI staff meeting notes, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 476)
  - Evaluation report (pilot phase), 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 477)
  - Evaluation and the shapes approach, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 478)
  - Evaluation survey-long form codebook, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 479)
  - Evaluation survey-short form codebook, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 480)
  - PRI evaluation-long form results, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 481)
  - PRI evaluation-short form results, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 482)
  - Rural developmental survey-objects, sample and sample items, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 483)
  - PRI evaluation expansion-memo draft, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 484)
  - Evaluation-Schwalbe comments (Box 16, Folder 485)
  - External evaluation-budget, notes on design, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 486)
  - External evaluation in subregions-Schedule, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 487)
  - External evaluation-memo and design and research components, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 488)
  - External evaluation team report and 4-24-79 memo (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - External evaluation planning, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 490)
  - External evaluation correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 491)
  - Evaluation forum notes, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 492)
  - External evaluation-working papers, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 493)
  - PRI short form survey-organizational affiliation breakdown (Box 16, Folder 494)
  - PRI external evaluation schedule, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 495)
  - PRI external evaluation report, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 496)
  - Rural development survey-preliminary material, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 497)
  - California Kellogg program, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Kellogg Foundation, annual report, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 499)
  - Pennsylvania Kellogg program (Box 17, Folder 500)
  - Relevant readings (Box 17, Folder 501)
  - Relevant readings (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - SW Minnesota Kellogg program, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - PRI news clippings, 1976-1980 (Box 17, Folder 504)
  - Re. PRI forum working papers, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 505)
  - Re. PRI forum-current planning, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 506)
  - PRI press release, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 507)
  - PRI annual reports, 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 508)
  - Re. Public forum, 1977-1980 (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - PRI forum newsletters, 1976-1981 (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - Subregion reports, 1978-1981 (Box 17, Folder 511-512)
  - PRI annual report, 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 513)
  - PRI report: Options For Rural Public Service Delivery, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 514)